<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="intro_descr">
        <item>Ordena productos de cualquier establecimiento o restaurante en tu ciudad.</item>
        <item> Nuestros mensajeros efectuarán la compra o buscarán tu pedido y lo llevarán donde estés en minutos.
        </item>
        <item>Haz tus pedidos de inmediato o coordina para una fecha posterior.
            Todo de una manera segura a través de nuestro app.        </item>
        <item>Elige de nuestro menú o ingresa “Otros” para pedidos especiales.        </item>
        <item>Ingresa información adicional tal como nombre de contacto o a quién debemos entregar tu envío.</item>
        <item>Te mostraremos el costo del servicio y podrás verificar tu información de contacto para estar siempre comunicados.</item>
        <item>Confirma tu método de pago o agrega uno nuevo</item>
        <item>Rastrea a tu mensajero en tiempo real de una manera constante y segura</item>
        <item>Calificar asegura brindarte un mejor servicio siempre.</item>
        <item>La factura llegará vía correo electrónico con todos los detalles de tu transacción.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="itro_titles">
        <item>Anything you want</item>
        <item> Anywhere you are </item>
        <item>Anytime you want it \n Safety</item>
        <item>Choice what you want buy or ship </item>
        <item>Choice the name of origin and the name of delivery</item>
        <item>Verify the info registered</item>
        <item>Pay</item>
        <item>Track your shippment</item>
        <item>Score your messenger</item>
        <item>Get your bill</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tab_titles">
        <item>Shipment</item>
        <item>Buy / Deliver</item>
        <item>Transactions</item>
    </string-array>


    <array name="incidents_faq_titles">
        <item>Service cancelled</item>
        <item>I can’t write the address properly</item>
        <item>Issuess to talk with the messenger</item>
        <item>Comunication issues with CDA</item>
        <item>Issues in maps traceablity</item>
        <item>I have a cancellation rate</item>
        <item>Promo code issues</item>
        <item>The messenger is not the one in the profile</item>
        <item>I don’t get any service check points</item>
        <item>Bill issues</item>
        <item>Invitations not sended</item>
        <item>The price doesn’t appears</item>
    </array>

    <array name="incidents_faq_bodies">
        <item>Turn off and on your mobile or reset it. If trouble persist please contact our help
            center.
        </item>
        <item>Verify the adress or input the points manually. If trouble persist please contact our
            help center.
        </item>
        <item>If you have repeatedly tried and are unable to communicate with your courier, please
            try our help center.
        </item>
        <item>Please email to us so we can provide you personal help.</item>
        <item>Turn on the GPS in your mobile. If trouble persist please contact our help center.
        </item>
        <item>Please contact our help center.</item>
        <item>Verify the expiration date of the promo, If trouble persist please contact our help
            center.
        </item>
        <item>Please send us an email to:</item>
        <item>Check that the signal of your mobile be optimal. If trouble persist please contact
            your messenger, and contact to our help center.
        </item>
        <item>If you need a tax bill, check the option that appears in the electronic bill and we
            deliver it to your email, if you had an unknow payment please contact our Help center.
        </item>
        <item>Please, contact our help center.</item>
        <item>Please, contact our help center.</item>
    </array>


    <array name="faq_titles">
        <item>What is entreGO?</item>
        <item>How to ask a delivery?</item>
        <item>How much I pay for a service?</item>
        <item>Does entreGO delivers in my address?</item>
        <item>What is the schedule?</item>
        <item>Who are the messengers?</item>
        <item>Can I book a service?</item>
        <item>What can I ask for?</item>
        <item>What payment methods are accepted?</item>
        <item>It’s my credit card protected?</item>
        <item>How does the payment realizes?</item>
        <item>How can I refund?</item>
        <item>I want a cancellation</item>
        <item>What if I had to modify my delivery</item>
        <item>Do I need to tip the messenger?</item>
        <item>How can I exchange a promo code?</item>
        <item>Can I ask for a multiple delivery in a service?</item>
        <item>Does my shippment has a warranty?</item>
    </array>

    <array name="faq_body">
        <item>EntreGO is transforming shipment, allowing anyone to send or receive what they want,
            whenever they want. Our revolutionary on-demand platform connects businesses and people
            with an extensive network of independent messengers through your smartphone or computer.
            In seconds and in an easy and safe way you can solve all your deliver problems knowing
            the status of your order in real time.
        </item>
        <item>Just has to follow this simple steps
            \n 1. Select one of our categories
            \n 2.Set the address of origin and delivery of your entreGO
            \n3. Request the service
            \n4. Relax and wait for entreGo to comes
            \n 5 Score the service
        </item>
        <item>
            Once you request your delivery antes an approximately fee will display
        </item>
        <item>EntreGO has just started operations in Panama Bella Vista and San Francisco
            specifically
        </item>
        <item>The messengers are available from 7:30 to 22:00 all days of the week
        </item>
        <item>
            Messengers are independent people with free time and a vehicle who just wants to made
            use of them and help you get your shipments done fast and safe
        </item>

        <item>
            Of course, you can book all the services you want! just. set the time you want to get them.
        </item>
        <item>
            request us to buy any product or send any delivery
            \n request us anything up to B/. 250.00 and a messenger will brought and deliver it for you
        </item>
        <item>
            Register your credit card in our website or app and you could pay with VISA or MASTER CARD safely and automatically\n
            To our messengers. Once the service is done through the bank terminal you can pay with Visa, Master Card and key card.\n
            You can also pay in cash to the messenger once the service is done.\n
            Registering your Paypal account on our website or in the application you can pay safely and automatically once the service is done.
        </item>
        <item>
            Our payment system is totally safe. Once your card is add in our system, it is cypher according to Visa / Master Card standards and only decoded every time a payment is made, which guarantees that your data is not stored or visible at any other time. This same system is used by the best companies in the world.
        </item>
        <item>
            Payment is made through the application, the web or the messenger only when the service has been validated by the client. The affiliate will ask you to sign the delivery and at that time we will proceed to charge you for the service and the purchase, if any.
        </item>
        <item>
            In entrust we take care of contacting the affiliates, who act as messengers. The affiliate makes the purchase on your behalf. In this way you continue to be the buyer and final consumer of the product. Any return or complaint about the product will be made directly in the local trade by the consumer, although we would like you to communicate through our call center. At entrGO we have a liability insurance to respond to any situation.
        </item>
        <item>
            Do you need to cancel it? Get in touch with our call center as soon as possible. If the order has already been accepted by the member, you must assume the costs of transportation and, if the purchase has been made, the costs of the product.
        </item>
        <item>
            If you want to change it just have to contact the affiliate or the call center. As soon as the order is accepted, both have their phones to resolve any doubts that may arise in the most effective way.
        </item>
        <item>
            Whatever you chosse.\n
            If you think they deserve it, why not?\n
            Messengers are free to accept tips but they never ask for them.
        </item>
        <item>
            In your profile in the app or in the website you\'ll find the promo code section, just enter it and you\'ll get your disscount applied
        </item>
        <item>
            Yes, of course!\n
            With entreGO you could had multiple deliveries in each of your services, just add the address where you want entreGO to deliver it
        </item>
        <item>
            In addition to having a liability insurance you can also track your shipment in real-time trought your app or web browser.
        </item>
    </array>

    <array name="cancel_reasons">
        <item>I charge cancellation fee</item>
        <item>Lost things</item>
        <item>Rate doubts</item>
        <item>I had problems with the route </item>
        <item>Feedback on the messenger</item>
        <item>Service comments</item>
        <item>Comments on the arrival of my package</item>
        <item>Troubles with billing</item>
    </array>
</resources>